Fear takes a new shape
The Tall Man is a horror, mystery, thriller film directed by Pascal Laugier.
When her child goes missing, a mother looks to unravel the legend of
the Tall Man, an entity who allegedly abducts children.
Julia Denning, played by Jessica Biel.
Jenny, played by Jodelle Ferland.
Lt Dodd, played by Stephen McHattie.
Sheriff Chestnut, played by William B. Davis.
Tracy, played by Samantha Ferris.
Mrs. Johnson, played by Colleen Wheeler.
The Tall Man is a 2012 Canadian-French mystery-horror film
written and directed by Pascal Laugier.
It was filmed in the Kootenay region of Southeastern
British Columbia and stars Jessica Biel.
The film is set in a small former mining town where poverty is rife
and children are disappearing on a regular basis.
The abductions are blamed on a local legend called "the Tall Man".
Jessica Biel plays a widowed nurse whose child is abducted,
leading her on a desperate chase to recover him.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.